[
  {
  "question": "Which Japanese food is a savory pancake cooked on a griddle?",
  "difficulty": "medium",
  "answers": [
    "Okonomiyaki",
    "Sashimi",
    "Onigiri",
    "Mochi"
  ],
  "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Japan's highest mountain?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": ["Mount Haku", "Mount Fuji", "Mount Aso", "Mount Tate"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which season is associated with red maple leaves (momiji) in Japan?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": ["Spring", "Summer", "Autumn", "Winter"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Japanese city is famous for its snow festival featuring ice sculptures?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": ["Sapporo", "Sendai", "Fukuoka", "Okayama"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the traditional Japanese tea ceremony called?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": ["Sado", "Judo", "Kendo", "Shodo"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese writing system used for foreign words?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": ["Katakana", "Hiragana", "Kanji", "Romaji"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Japanese city is famous for the Gion Matsuri festival?",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "answers": [
      "Kyoto",
      "Nagoya",
      "Hiroshima",
      "Sendai"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Which Japanese castle was the seat of the Tokugawa shogunate?",
  "difficulty": "medium",
  "answers": [
    "Edo Castle",
    "Himeji Castle",
    "Matsumoto Castle",
    "Osaka Castle"
  ],
  "correctIndex": 0
},
{
  "question": "What is the Japanese term for a traditional inn?",
  "difficulty": "medium",
  "answers": [
    "Ryokan",
    "Izakaya",
    "Minshuku",
    "Tateyama"
  ],
  "correctIndex": 0
},
{
  "question": "What is the Japanese term for \"new year\"?",
  "difficulty": "medium",
  "answers": [
    "Shogatsu",
    "Obon",
    "Tanabata",
    "Hinamatsuri"
  ],
  "correctIndex": 0
}

]
